[{"question": " hi joey, how ya doin&#146;?", "answer": " great! roomie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " huh, yeah i guess we are roommates now.", "answer": " yeah! well, now that you brought it up, our fridge is broken. we have to get a new one. now, i checked around and your half is $400. thanks a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i&#146;m not paying for half of that! i&#146;m only staying here until my apartment gets fixed.", "answer": " look rach, my parents bought this fridge just after i was born, okay? now, i have never had a problem with it. then you show up and it breaks! what does that tell ya&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " that refrigerators don&#146;t live as long as people.", "answer": " all right, now you know that the atm will only lets you take out 300 at a time, i&#146;ll take a check for the other hundred.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " you&#146;re jokin&#146; right?", "answer": " of course i&#146;m jokin&#146;! i don&#146;t take checks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi! hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " do you guys know any cute guys?", "answer": " well, of course i do! my good friend joey over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. thank you chandler.", "answer": " anyway, there&#146;s this big charity ball this weekend and ralph lauren bought a table, so i kinda have to go&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what&#146;s the charity?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, something either trees or disease&#151;ralph mumbles a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " does ralph mumble when you&#146;re not paying attention?", "answer": " yeah! it&#146;s weird. but the thing is need to find a date.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, what kind of guy are you looking for?", "answer": " well, someone that has his own tux, or has the ability to rent a tux.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " so he has to be a male who has at least $50.", "answer": " ooh! so close.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " hey everybody!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey uh, this is elizabeth.", "answer": " oh hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " i&#146;m the student.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  isn&#146;t she cute?  no!", "answer": " y&#146;know, this is probably none of my business, but weren&#146;t you guys supposed to not be seen in public together?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh, we&#146;re not together.", "answer": " oh no-no-no, we&#146;re just two people who happen to run into each other here at the coffee house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, sly.", "answer": " well, i really wanted to meet you guys, but i have to run. i&#146;ll see you later?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " bye ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " oops! i did not mean to run into you like that sir.", "answer": " oh that is quite all right ma&#146;am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " so, why is she leaving? is it a school night and she has a lot of homework to do?", "answer": " yes, her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, tell her good luck with that.", "answer": " anyone else? huh? bring &#145;em on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oo! when&#146;s her birthday?!", "answer": " i don&#146;t know rachel, why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " well, y&#146;know it&#146;s just been so long since i&#146;ve been to chuckie cheese.", "answer": " oh, i like elizabeth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " well thanks!", "answer": " yeah. in fact, i like her so much you tell her i want my cookies early this year! y&#146;know, a box of thin mints and some tag-a-longs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey-hey come on you guys, give him a break. ross, seriously, how&#146;s it going with her?", "answer": " well, actually it&#146;s been great. she&#146;s 20 so she&#146;s not looking for anything too serious, which is perfect for me right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " well that is great. and seriously, she seems very nice.", "answer": " thanks. i know you guys like to give me a hard time and all, but it really means a lot to me that you like her. just knowing that you guys are&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " chandler, do you think we talk about our relationship enough?", "answer": " yeah. do we have any fruit roll-ups?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay, i just thought of the perfect guy for rachel to take to her thing.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s so funny because we found someone too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s good, i guess she&#146;ll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.", "answer": " why would our guy be a weirdo?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " &#145;cause that&#146;s just your taste.", "answer": "  rachel is not going to pick your stupid guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh yeah?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " a face ass?", "answer": " a chin dimple!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well, uh y&#146;know, our guy works with chandler and he&#146;s really nice and smart and he&#146;s a great dresser!", "answer": " have you seen your guy&#146;s body?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no, our guy is just a floating head.", "answer": " well my guy is spectacular. okay? he&#146;s a massage client and one time umm, when he was on the table, i looked at it. and i mean all of it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " you&#146;re not supposed to look!", "answer": " oh yeah, like there are police for that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  wait! you look? you-you massaged me.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " all right fine, your guy may have a great body, but our guy is really funny.", "answer": " oh, chandler funny?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " our guy&#146;s a great dancer!", "answer": " my guy is well read.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " our guy has great hair.", "answer": " my guy has great teeth!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " our guy smells incredible.", "answer": "  do you want our guy to be your guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well, you&#133;don&#146;t look good joe.", "answer": " the fridge broke. i have to eat everything. cold cuts, ice cream, limes&#151;hey, what was in that brown jar?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " that&#146;s still in there?!", "answer": " not anymore. so anyway, how do you want to pay me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " is this a service you&#146;re providing me?", "answer": " no! no! no! for my new fridge&#151;our new fridge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " our new fridge? i don&#146;t live here anymore.", "answer": " so what? look, suppose we were a divorced couple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " and i got custody of the kid, right? now suppose the kid dies and-and i gotta buy a new kid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  okay&#133;", "answer": "  give me $400!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " professor geller?", "answer": " hmm?  oh, a student i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " i was wondering if i could talk to you for a moment?", "answer": " yes, yes of course, what-what would this be regarding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " making out in your office.", "answer": " shh!  of course, why don&#146;t we go inside?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh-ooh!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " doorknob! doorknob!", "answer": " oh! sorry! umm, i actually do need to talk to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " oh, okay. what-what about?", "answer": " spring vacation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " spring vacation.", "answer": " yeah, we have time off and a lot of people are going on trips&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " professor geller!", "answer": "  yes, professor feesen-sen-stenlger&#133; i&#146;ll be with you in one moment.  so, i will take one box of the thin mints.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " you don&#146;t understand! elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her! is that taking it slow?! no, i&#146;m not ready for this! okay? what-what do i tell her?", "answer": " just tell her the truth! tell her you&#146;re not ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " i can do that. oh-oh, what if she gets upset?", "answer": " then you distract her with a barbie doll.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " what the hell are you doing?", "answer": " what? what the hell am i doing? you just broke my fridge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " what?! what? how do you, how do you even know its broken?!", "answer": " oh-ho-ho, you think i don&#146;t know what breaks my fridge? excuse me!  well what do you know! broken! that&#146;ll be $400!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " joey, i saw you push him!", "answer": "  you pushed him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " joey, i did not break this! okay?  that has been broken for a while.", "answer": " all right. chandler, do you remember how i told you about our fridge?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " i still haven&#146;t gotten a check for your half yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " do not give him any money!", "answer": " i&#146;m not talking to you! you broke my fridge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you wanted to see me professor geller?", "answer": " yes. yes! please, come in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oo-oo!", "answer": " doorknob?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah, it kinda grows on you.  actually, i wanted to finish talking to you about uh, spring vacation.", "answer": " oh good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " look, i&#133;  look, i&#146;m having a great time with you and i just don&#146;t want us to move to fast or put to much pressure on us. so, i&#146;m sorry i just don&#146;t think we should go away together yet. it&#146;s-it&#146;s too soon.", "answer": " ross, i think you misunderstood what i was saying. i just wanted to tell you that i&#146;m going to florida for a couple weeks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no. i think you misunderstood what i was saying. what i meant was&#133;", "answer": " you are so adorable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! how did it go with elizabeth?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " huh? oh-oh, it was fine. uh, it was just a misunderstanding. she didn&#146;t want me to go with her. she just wanted to let me know that she&#146;s going to florida for spring vacation.", "answer": " wait a minute, is she going for spring vacation or is she going for spring break?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " what&#146;s-what&#146;s the difference?", "answer": " well, spring vacation is doing nice things with your grandparents. spring break you&#146;re doing frat guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey, y&#146;know what? not all spring breaks are like that.", "answer": " what did you do on yours?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i went to egypt with my dad.", "answer": " i can see it now, &quot;look dad, it&#146;s the sphinx!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " hey, i think elizabeth is a little more serious than, &quot;spring break!&quot;  all right? i mean she&#146;s taken my class!", "answer": " and slept with the professor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna call her.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hey! you guys umm, i want you to meet sebastian.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " we just uh, we just met at the newsstand. we both grabbed for the last field &amp; stream.  what? i read that.", "answer": " can i get you a cup of coffee?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " rachel, what the hell is this?!", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " you ask us to find you a guy and you come traipsing in here with your own!", "answer": " you found me a guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " yes! we found you a really cute and funny guy from chandler&#146;s work!", "answer": " yeah and i-i found you one too who is not a weirdo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, y&#146;know what though you guys? i really appreciate that but i think i&#146;m just gonna take sebastian to the charity.", "answer": " are you sure?! because our guy smells incredible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh, thank you.", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " so, sebastian, do you do any volunteer work?", "answer": " uh, no not really. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " no reason, it&#146;s just i know a single guy that cares about other people.", "answer": " are you funny?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " what are you guys doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " are you funny? tell us a joke!", "answer": " look, i just wanted to have coffee with rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " well, so do a lot of people.", "answer": " actually, i uh, i gotta get going.  give me a call sometime.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh, but y&#146;know, no, you didn&#146;t give me your phone number.", "answer": " okay! see you later!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i cannot believe you guys! he was really nice and he left because of you!", "answer": " yeah, but sebastian? what is that? a cat&#146;s name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yeah, y&#146;know what i noticed rachel? he scares easy. is that the kind of guy you&#146;d like to take to a ball? &quot;hey sebastian, would you like to dance?&quot;  &quot;uhh, okay&#151;i gotta go!&quot;", "answer": " all right guys stop it. rachel, we&#146;re very sorry that is a very insensitive thing for us to do. and y&#146;know what? let us make it up to you, we have two really great guys for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah! what have you got to lose? y&#146;know you might even end up with someone really special  if you pick my guy.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " okay, so you will meet our guys?", "answer": " yes, i&#146;ll meet &#145;em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " okay now it doesn&#146;t matter which one you choose, y&#146;know? it&#146;s completely up to you. our guy is perfect, or you can go out with the guy phoebe deemed not good enough to go out with herself.", "answer": "  pheebs! there you are! okay, you broke my fridge; you owe me 400 bucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " okay sure!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ooh, technically you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts on your last ten auditions.", "answer": " call it even?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  well, there you are! so what did elizabeth say?", "answer": " well, it turns out that she is going to daytona for spring break woo-hoo. that means, that means wet t-shirt contests, guys doing shots off of girl&#146;s bodies, waking up next to people you don&#146;t even know&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " man, she is going to have a great time! is she staying at the hotel corona?", "answer": " you know the hotels?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " sure! i was there! spring break &#146;81! woo-hoo!", "answer": " in 1981 you were 13!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " so what? i drove down, sold t-shirts, had a blast. and y&#146;know who knows how to party? drunk college chicks.", "answer": " okay, she can&#146;t go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " ross, you can&#146;t tell her not to go. you just started dating.", "answer": " then what am i supposed to do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " nothing, you just have to be cool with it.", "answer": " well, what is she goes down and-and sleeps with a bunch of guys?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i&#146;m so glad you&#146;re going on this trip!", "answer": " yeah! i&#146;ve been working so hard this semester. i really need to go crazy y&#146;know, blow off some steam.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " sure. sure. look i don&#146;t, i don&#146;t know if your plans are finalized yet, but umm, hey i-i know another great way to blow off steam.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " are you into crafts at all?", "answer": " ross, are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " it&#146;s a bathing suit?", "answer": " to wear in front of people?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " is that supportive?", "answer": " is this?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " good-good-good-good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " we&#146;re really glad you decided to meet our guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh&#133;", "answer": " you&#146;re gonna like him so much. so umm, when do you want to meet him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know. i know i don&#146;t work late tomorrow night.", "answer": " tomorrow night is good. tomorrow night is good, but uh, y&#146;know what? why put off something till tomorrow that you can do right now?  eldad come here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " eldad, this is rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " well-well a little blind sided but y&#146;know good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " eldad, sit down.  move over! move over now!", "answer": " i&#151;ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " okay! okay! we can take a hint!   what are you doing here?!", "answer": " this is patrick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi.  okay, you&#146;re too late okay? because she&#146;s already with our guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  oh my god, you&#146;re right! i am too late; they&#146;re sitting on the couch and talking!  come on!  rachel?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " this is patrick.", "answer": " oh, hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " yeah, this is the guy i was telling you about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah. and believe me, this suit does not do justice to what&#146;s underneath it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " oh-okay, but pheebs?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " i&#146;m just sort of in the middle of something.", "answer": " oh! okay! yeah, that&#146;s okay.  have a seat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " no! you can&#146;t do that!", "answer": " maybe i should go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  sit down! we&#146;re winning!", "answer": " okay, y&#146;know what? maybe i should go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": "  no-no-no-no! have a seat! have a seat!", "answer": " rachel! rachel! you haven&#146;t touched eldad&#146;s hair!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;m good.", "answer": " rachel? patrick is really rich.  give her some money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " y&#146;know what phoebe? this isn&#146;t really worth the free massage.", "answer": " that&#146;s right patrick, bye-bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " no-no! don&#146;t dance for me! please? don&#146;t!  what is the matter with you guys?", "answer": " yeah, okay, let&#146;s talk it out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " i&#133; am i the only one that this is embarrassing for?", "answer": " i&#146;m a little embarrassed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " i&#146;ll tell ya who should be embarrassed! it&#146;s you guys! come on! this is ridiculous! thank you very much, but i do not need you to get me a date!", "answer": " then why did she ask us to&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " i am still talking!! and then you chase away the one guy that i actually liked! i mean, no offense to you guys. really! i mean  congratulations on all the cash,  and-and y&#146;know&#151;&#151;wow! you do have very soft hair! but i would much rather go to the ball all by myself than go through anymore of this! good-bye!  now do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?!", "answer": " yes, papaya extract.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " so uh, have a great time down there.", "answer": " i will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " yeah. and did you, did you pack that bathing suit?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " it was pretty funny when i, when i hid it for a while, huh? anyway, umm, i-i am worried about that bathing suit, not because it&#146;s revealing which i&#146;m fine with, no i&#146;m concerned about your health, sun exposure.", "answer": " oh, don&#146;t worry i have plenty of sun block, it&#146;s spf-30.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " well, if what&#146;s in the bottle is actually 30. i mean sometimes you get 30, sometimes it&#146;s-it&#146;s get 4, and i swear to god more often than not it&#146;s just milk.", "answer": " ross, it&#146;s going to be okay. i&#146;m not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys. i really like you. i like how things are going between us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! i&#146;m just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " okay. cool.", "answer": " oh hey! here they are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " rachel, we&#146;re sorry for pushing those guys on you.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s all right! y&#146;know, i ended up having a really good time. y&#146;know, the charity was a big success and they raised a lot of money and awareness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " so what was it for anyway?", "answer": " i wanna say a disease.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " i just got this really weird message from ross. he said turn on mtv.", "answer": " huh. all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " oh-oh professor geller.", "answer": " ahh, to be 13 again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}]